[
    {
        "question": "Is it true that 1 + 1 = 2 ?",
        "answer": "true",
        "options": ["true", "false"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it true that 1 + 1 = 4 ?",
        "answer": "false",
        "options": ["true", "false"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The uk is bigger than Japan?",
        "answer": "true",
        "options": ["true", "false"]
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 7.5 = ?",
        "answer": "37.5",
        "options": ["32.5", "34.5", "37.5", "40.5"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kimchi is Korean food?",
        "answer": "true",
        "options": ["true", "false"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Tenerife island belongs to Europe??",
        "answer": "true",
        "options": ["true", "false"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Is 3477 prime number? ?",
        "answer": "false",
        "options": ["true", "false"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Bubble waffle have a bubble inside?",
        "answer": "false",
        "options": ["true", "false"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vodka is originated in Russia?",
        "answer": "false",
        "options": ["true", "false"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ale is originated in England?",
        "answer": "true",
        "options": ["true", "false"]
    }
]